Finding Aid for the Walter E. Bennett Photographic Collection LSC.0686
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 5: Batched negatives, 1953-1967; 3 boxes.
  - Passman, Otto., 1962 September. (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Patman, Wright., 1962 July. (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Pearson, Drew., 1954 April 9. (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Pepper, Claude., 1967 March. (Box 8, Folder 117)
    Shots of the Representative (D- Florida) in his Washington D.C. office.
  - Peterson, Esther., [2 folders].
    Assistant Secretary of Labor.
    - ., 1964 April (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - ., 1966 April (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Porter, Katherine Anne., 1962 March. (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Proxmire, William., 1967 January. (Box 8, Folder 121)
    Shots of the Senator (D- Wisconsin) in his Washington D.C. office.
  - Rayburn, Sam., [4 folders].
    Representative.
    - ., 1958 January (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ., 1959 February (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ., 1960 January (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Shots of the Speaker of the House with Richard Nixon at the Joint Session of Congress to Announce Presidential Ballots Results., 1961 February. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Redstone Guided Missile., 1956 February 1. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Shots of Dr. Wernher von Braun and Major General John Bruce Medaris with the Army Pentagon model.
  - Republican Congressional Dinner., 1967 March. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Includes shots of Gov. George Romney (R-Michigan), Richard Nixon, Barry Goldwater, Ronald Reagan, and Sen. George Murphy (R- California).
  - Reston, James. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Includes shots with son.
  - Reuther, Walter., 1961 June. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    President of United Auto Workers.
  - Rhodes, John J., 1966 August. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Rhyne, Charles., 1962 March. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham., [3 folders].
    - Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare., 1961 April. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Senator (D- Connecticut)., 1966 May 6. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Shots of the Senator (D- Connecticut) in his office., 1967 April. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson., 1955 January 21. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Rostow, Walt., 1961 March. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Deputy Assistant for National Security.
  - Rowan, Carl., 1965 August. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Rusk, Dean., [5 folders].
    - ., 1961 May (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - ., 1961 July (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Shots of the Secretary of State with Director if the I.C.A. Henry Labouisse., 1961 July. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - ., 1963 March (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - ., 1964 April (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Includes shots with Lyndon Johnson.
  - Sandberg, Carl., 1959 November. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Saud, King., [2 folders].
    - Shots of the King in Washington D.C and Annapolis., 1957 January. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Shots with Eisenhower., 1957 February. (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Jr., 1961 July. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    White House advisor.
  - Schultze, Charles L., 1966 September. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Shots of the Director of the Bureau of the Budget in his Washington D.C. office.
  - Seaborg, Glenn., 1961 January. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Chairman of the Atomic Energy Commission.
  - Sengi, Antonio., 1959 October. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Selassie, Haile., [2 folders].
    - Shots of the Ethiopian Emperor with Eisenhower., 1954 June 4. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Shots of the Ethiopian Emperor with Kennedy., 1963 October. (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Shriver, Sargent., 1962 February 12. (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Shots of Sargent with family.
  - Slim, Mongi., 1958 January. (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Space Candidates., 1959 April. (Box 9, Folder 33)
    Shots of astronaut candidates.
  - Stans, Maurice H., 1955 October 16. (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Assistant Postmaster General.
  - Stengel, Casey., 1958 July. (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Stennis, John., 1965 August. (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Stevenson, Adlai., 1958 April. (Box 9, Folder 37)
    Shots of Stevenson addressing the Reciprocal Trade Program.
  - Stewart, Potter., 1961 July. (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Stravinsky, Igor., 1961 July. (Box 9, Folder 39)
    Shots of the conductor with singer Helga Pilarczyk.
  - Suhrawardy, Hussein Shaheed., 1957 July. (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Sukarno., 1956 May 31. (Box 9, Folder 41)
    Shots of the Indonesian President during his Washington D.C. visit.
  - Summit Conference between U.S. and Vietnamese officials at Honolulu., 1966 February. (Box 9, Folder 42)
    Includes shots of Major General Nguyen Duc Thang, Construction Minister Nguyen Ngoc Linh, Press Officer for the U.N. Kab Van Tri, Minister of Agriculture Bui Diem, Special Assistant to the Prime Minister Ky David Bell, and Orville Freeman.
  - Supreme Court., 1958 December. (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Supreme Court Justices., 1965 November. (Box 9, Folder 44)
    Includes shots of Byron White, William Brennan, Potter Stewart, Abe Fortas, Tom C. Clark, Hugo Black, Earl Warren, William O. Douglas, and John Harlan.
  - Taylor, Maxwell., [2 folders].
    - ., 1960 February (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - ., 1961 June 30 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Teller, Edward., 1958 April. (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Thompson, Llewellyn., 1958 January. (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Toure, Sekou., 1959 November. (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Truman, Harry., 1958 April. (Box 9, Folder 50)
    Shots of Truman at Truman dinner.
  - Tydings, Joseph., 1967 August. (Box 9, Folder 51)
    Senator (D- Maryland).
  - Vaughn, Harry., 1955 October 14. (Box 9, Folder 52)
    Major General.
  - Veeck, Bill., 1962 July. (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - U Thant, Maha Thray Sithu., 1962 September 13. (Box 9, Folder 54)
    Shots of U Thant with Dean Rusk, Adlai Stevenson, and John Kennedy.
  - Walker, Edward., 1962 April. (Box 9, Folder 55)
    Shots of the General with Sen. John Stennis.
  - Wallace, George., 1963 July. (Box 9, Folder 56)
    Governor (D- Alabama).
  - Walton, William., [2 folders].
    - Former Kennedy aide from New York., 1961 January. (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Artist and friend of John Kennedy., 1961 March. (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Warren, Earl., 1954 January 24. (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Watson, Marvin., 1967 January. (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Westmoreland, William C., 1964 January. (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Wheeler, Burton., 1954 May 28. (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - White, Byron "Whizzer"., [2 folders].
    Deputy Attorney General.
    - ., 1962 February (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - ., 1962 April (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Wolfson, Louis., 1955 June 10. (Box 9, Folder 65)
    Shots of Wolfson testifying before Sen. Lehmanis Committee on proxy rights.
  - World Peace Through Law., 1965 September 15. (Box 9, Folder 66)
    Includes shots of Richard Nixon, Charles Rhyne, and Henry Luce.
  - Wurf, Jerry., 1966 July. (Box 9, Folder 67)
    Of the American Federation of State, Count and Municipal Employees.